When we're talking about how we reinforce patriarchy as women, the emphasis we place on our pussies, we think that's the only thing we have to value.
When I raise the conversation and many other women raise the conversation of choosing men who can actually tangibly benefit your life, especially financially, the rebuttal I get from most women is,
but what are you going to give in return? I don't want to have to have sex. Well, who said you have to do anything?
You think you have to give that man sex because you think that's the most valuable thing about yourself.
Actually, for me, sex isn't the most valuable thing that I can bring to a man's life.
My company, my influence, my jokes.
Are y'all listening? Do you get?
I have the ability to motivate people into being higher versions of themselves.
I have transformed broken b****s. I have transformed criminals too.
Listen, I've been there. I understand. I resonate with you, Amanda, where it's like we see the brokenness in people, whether they're men or women.
We just see people and we try so hard from a pure place to get them there.
But with men, they don't want to help themselves.
And this is why men keep patriarchy, even though men are harmed by patriarchy.